Guide to the David Daggett Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Smith, David (1767-1862), 1823 (Box 9, Folder 280)
  - Smith, John Cotton (1765-1845), 1785-1844 (Box 10, Folder 281-285)
  - Smith, Junius (1780-1853), 1806 (Box 10, Folder 286)
  - Smith, Nathan (1762-1829), 1815-1835 (Box 10, Folder 287-288)
  - Smith, Nathaniel (1762-1822), 1796-1820 (Box 10, Folder 289)
  - Smith, Samuel (1752-1839), 1814 (Box 10, Folder 290)
  - Smith, Truman (1791-1884), 1831-1846 (Box 10, Folder 291)
  - Smith, William (1762-1840), 1817 (Box 10, Folder 292)
  - Southard, Samuel Lewis (1787-1842), 1831 (Box 10, Folder 293)
  - Spencer, Ambrose (1765-1848), 1832, 1836 (Box 10, Folder 294)
  - Spencer, John Canfield (1788-1855), 1819 (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - Sprague, William Buell (1795-1876), 1828, 1847 (Box 11, Folder 296)
  - Spring, Gardiner (1785-1873), 1806-1817 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Stanley, George Washington (1775-1854), 1804-1829 (Box 11, Folder 298)
  - Staples, Seth Perkins (1776-1861), 1799-1817 (Box 11, Folder 299)
  - Stearns, Elisha (1776-1850), 1797-1816 (Box 11, Folder 300)
  - Stebbins, Josiah (1766-1829), 1810 (Box 11, Folder 301)
  - Stiles, Isaac (1763-1795), 1786 (Box 11, Folder 302)
  - Stockton, Richard (1764-1828), 1813-1816 (Box 11, Folder 303)
  - Stone, William Leete (1792-1844), 1819 (Box 11, Folder 304)
  - Storrs, Henry Randolph (1787-1837), 1812, 1832 (Box 11, Folder 305)
  - Storrs, William Lucius (1795-1861), 1830-1840 (Box 11, Folder 306)
  - Story, Joseph (1779-1845), 1818-1826 (Box 11, Folder 307)
  - Strong, Nehemiah (1729-1807), 1799, 1803 (Box 11, Folder 308)
  - Sturges, Jonathan (1740-1819), 1805 (Box 11, Folder 309)
  - Sturges, Lewis Burr (1763-1844), 1801-1818 (Box 11, Folder 310)
  - Sullivan, Lucas, 1820-1821 (Box 11, Folder 311)
  - Sullivan, William (1774-1839), 1805 (Box 11, Folder 312)
  - Sullivant, William Starling (1803-1873), 1821-1825 (Box 11, Folder 313)
  - Swift, Zephaniah (1729-1823), 1792-1818 (Box 11, Folder 314)
  - T - General (Box 11, Folder 315)
  - Tallmadge, Benjamin (1754-1835), 1789-1800 (Box 11, Folder 316)
  - Terry, Nathaniel (1768-1844), 1798, 1823 (Box 11, Folder 317)
  - Tichenor, Isaac (1754-1838), 1820-1823 (Box 11, Folder 318)
  - Tomlinson, Gideon (1780-1854), 1820-1833 (Box 11, Folder 319)
  - Toucey, Isaac (1792-1869), 1823 (Box 11, Folder 320)
  - Tracy, Elisha, 1813-1818 (Box 11, Folder 321)
  - Tracy, Uriah (1755-1807), 1794, 1807 (Box 11, Folder 322)
  - Truop, Robert (1757-1832), 1813 (Box 11, Folder 323)
  - Trumbull, Benjamin (1735-1820), 1814 (Box 11, Folder 324)
  - Trumbull, Benjamin (1769-1850), 1828 (Box 11, Folder 325)
  - Trumbull, John (1756-1843), 1818 (Box 11, Folder 326)
  - Trumbull, Jonathan (1740-18-9), 1802 (Box 11, Folder 327)
  - Trumbull, Joseph (1782-1861), 1826, 1840 (Box 11, Folder 328)
  - Tudor, Samuel, 1813-1824 (Box 11, Folder 329)
  - Twining, Stephen (1767-1832), 1829 (Box 11, Folder 330)
  - Tyler, Samuel, 1784-1787 (Box 11, Folder 331)
  - Upson, Benoni (1750-1826), 1817, 1818 (Box 11, Folder 332)
  - V - General (Box 11, Folder 333)
  - Varnum, Joseph Bradley (1750/1751-1821), 1818 (Box 11, Folder 334)
  - Voight, Thomas, 1816 (Box 11, Folder 335)
  - W - General (Box 12, Folder 336)
  - Wadsworth, Daniel (1771-1848), 1822 (Box 12, Folder 337)
  - Wadsworth, Jeremiah (1743-1804), 1795-1797 (Box 12, Folder 338)
  - Waite, Henry Matson (1787-1869), 1840 (Box 12, Folder 339)
  - Wales, Leonard Eugene (1788-1823), 1814 (Box 12, Folder 340)
  - Walker, Joseph (1756-1810), 1801-1810 (Box 12, Folder 341)
  - Walsh, Robert (1784-1859), 1819 (Box 12, Folder 342)
  - Ward, Artemas (1762-1847), 1816 (Box 12, Folder 343)
  - Washburn, Seth, 1789-1819 (Box 12, Folder 344)
  - Washington, Bushrod (1762-1829), 1807, 1819 (Box 12, Folder 345)
  - Webster, Daniel (1782-1852), 1814-1848 (Box 12, Folder 346)
  - Webster, Noah (1758-1843), 1811-1813 (Box 12, Folder 347)
  - Welch, William Henry (1805-1862), 1828 (Box 12, Folder 348)
  - Wells, John (1770-1823) (Box 12, Folder 349)
  - White, Charles Coomer (1763-1796), 1786 (Box 12, Folder 350)
  - White, Dyer (1762-1841), 1795 (Box 12, Folder 351)
  - Whitman, Lemuel (1780-1841), 1824 (Box 12, Folder 352)
  - Whitney, Eli (1765-1825), 1800, 1818 (Box 12, Folder 353)
  - Williams, John (1778-1837), 1819-1822 (Box 12, Folder 354)
  - Williams, Thomas Scott (1777-1861), 1817-1836 (Box 12, Folder 355)
  - Williston, Payson (1763-1856), 1846 (Box 12, Folder 356)
  - Wirt, William (1772-1834), 1819-1830 (Box 12, Folder 357)
  - Wolcott, Alexander, 1809-1818 (Box 12, Folder 358)
  - Wolcott, Oliver (1760-1833), 1794, 1803 (Box 12, Folder 359)
  - Wood, Joseph (1779-1856), 1804, 1813 (Box 12, Folder 360)
  - Woodbridge, William (1780-1861), 1818 (Box 12, Folder 361)
  - Woodworth, John (1768-1858), 1833 (Box 12, Folder 362)
  - Woolsey, William Walton (1766-1839), 1812 (Box 12, Folder 363)
  - Wooster, Mary (Clap) (1729-1807), undated (Box 12, Folder 364)
  - Yale College, 1833-1848 (Box 12, Folder 365)
  - Yates, Andrew (1773-1844), 1817 (Box 12, Folder 366)
  - Young, David, 1804, 1817 (Box 12, Folder 367)
  - UNIDENTIFIED, 1846 (Box 12, Folder 368)
- Writings, Series II
  - General, 1791-1841, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Oration before the Society of the Cincinnati, 1791 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Misc. writings re: Rev. John Gemmill, Circa 1801 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "Mr. Daggett's argument, before the General Assembly of the State of Connecticut, October, 1804, in the case of Certain Justices of the Peace…" rough draft for pamphlet. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Political Address to the People of Connecticut on the Gubernatorial Race of 1816 in Connecticut (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "To the Federal Freemen of Connecticut,", Circa 1816 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Substance of a speech delivered before the Senate on the question of the Internal Improvements Bill of, 1816/1817 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "Letter to the Hon. Judge Darling, November 7, 1833" (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "New Haven Sixty Years Ago and since,", Circa 1841 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous undated writings (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Legal briefs (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Law lectures, 1822-1848 (Box 13, Folder 3-4B)
  - Lecture notes taken by J. C. Loomis, 1829 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Lecture notes taken by J. C. Angus Manning, 1832-1833 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Lecture notes taken by Aaron Nichols Skinner, 1822-1824 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Special Files, Series III
  - Legal documents and business papers, 1782-1837 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Account book, 1826-1851 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Day book, 1812-1844 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Clippings (Box 14, Folder 4)